{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489188172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489188172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489514501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489514500"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489514590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489514589"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 015dc2ee-2197-4a14-b064-5c05d4857d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489526816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489526816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489527203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489527203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489527703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489527703"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489528058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489528058"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489528473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489528473"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489528955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489528955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489529191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489529191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489532380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489532379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489532418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489532418"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489533145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489533145"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489533550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489533550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489533853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489533852"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489534070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489534070"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489534273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489534273"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489534600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489534599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489534834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489534833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489538018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489538017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489538432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489538431"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489541044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489541043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489541256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489541256"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489541470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489541469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489544994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489544993"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489548789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489548789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489549824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489549823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489552586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489552585"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489552975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489552975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489553469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489553468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489553817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489553817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489554227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489554226"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489554710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489554709"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489554942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489554942"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489558194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489558193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489558234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489558233"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489558961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489558960"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489559366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489559365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489559668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489559667"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489559886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489559884"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489560091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489560091"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489560415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489560415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489560649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489560648"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489563280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489563279"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489563378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489563378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 5c4dcc0b-5813-49f4-a44e-07b06d7e7c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489577663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489577662"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 9e226f49-e9aa-4ee1-8a92-599234cec71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489588729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489588729"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 9e226f49-e9aa-4ee1-8a92-599234cec71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489591099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489591098"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 9e226f49-e9aa-4ee1-8a92-599234cec71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489613081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489613081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 9e226f49-e9aa-4ee1-8a92-599234cec71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489613185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489613185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 9e226f49-e9aa-4ee1-8a92-599234cec71a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489634669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489634669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_H_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489641323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489641323"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_Y_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489647979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489647979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489654600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489654599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_E_K"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489661206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489661206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_G_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489667843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489667842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_S_E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489674474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489674474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_R_E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489681125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489681125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_G_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489687748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489687747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489694386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489694386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489707571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489707571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 0925ffe0-4c67-41fd-96a8-3754e95a9587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489747705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489747705"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 777eb9b0-06dd-493f-88b5-11df201e7446"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489777622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489777622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 777eb9b0-06dd-493f-88b5-11df201e7446"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489841969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489841969"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 777eb9b0-06dd-493f-88b5-11df201e7446"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489842054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489842054"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 777eb9b0-06dd-493f-88b5-11df201e7446"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489851420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489851419"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 777eb9b0-06dd-493f-88b5-11df201e7446"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489868365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489868364"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 777eb9b0-06dd-493f-88b5-11df201e7446"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489880937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489880937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" b9f85910-5e08-4e59-b231-6a708832eff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489882749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489882749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" b9f85910-5e08-4e59-b231-6a708832eff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489882944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489882944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" b9f85910-5e08-4e59-b231-6a708832eff9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489914216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489914216"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489920432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489920432"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489923757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489923757"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489926521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489926521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489951305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489951305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489970811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489970811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548489993590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548489993590"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548490012815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548490012815"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548490035554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548490035554"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548490055528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548490055528"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548490076805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548490076802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548490076923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548490076923"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_105248"," gameId":" 942143d3-b592-4e3b-ae08-d4a8dc01c691"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}